{
    "mosaic": "Sandra",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Question": "VITAMINS, COD LIVER OIL & OTHER SUPPLEMENTS  (including sports nutrition/supplements) Frequency",
            "Top Answer": "\"Medium Users\" by 40.8%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Types Enriched with Probiotics",
            "Top Answer": "\"Occasionally\" by 35.08%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "VITAMINS, COD LIVER OIL & OTHER SUPPLEMENTS  (including sports nutrition/supplements) Used",
            "Top Answer": "\"All Users\" by 58.47%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "MEAT ALTERNATIVES (Including TOFU) (Main Shopper) Frequency",
            "Top Answer": "\"Less than once a WEEK\" by 9.27%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed High Fat Content",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 55.9%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "VITAMINS, COD LIVER OIL & OTHER SUPPLEMENTS  (including sports nutrition/supplements) Types",
            "Top Answer": "\"Multivitamins\" by 34.48%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "INSTANT SAVOURY SNACKS & READY TO EAT SALADS (including snack meals) (Adults) Frequency",
            "Top Answer": "\"Medium Users\" by 10.17%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed Artificial Preservatives",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 41.28%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed High Sugar Content",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 42.83%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Types Protein Enriched",
            "Top Answer": "\"Never\" by 40.07%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "INSTANT SAVOURY SNACKS & READY TO EAT SALADS (including snack meals) (Adults) Consumed",
            "Top Answer": "\"Non Users\" by 71.97%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed High Calorie Content",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 52.94%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "VITAMINS, COD LIVER OIL & OTHER SUPPLEMENTS  (including sports nutrition/supplements) Brands",
            "Top Answer": "\"OTHER BRANDS\" by 23.99%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD AND DIET Statements Not Applicable",
            "Top Answer": "\"I can't eat as healthily when I am trying to save on food costs\" by 1.67%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "BABY MILK AND BABY/JUNIOR FOODS (INCLUDING CEREALS, RUSKS, YOGURT AND FROMAGE FRAIS) (Main Shopper) Frequency Food",
            "Top Answer": "\"Medium Users\" by 2.77%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed Artificial Colouring/Flavourings",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 40.13%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Types Premium Ranges",
            "Top Answer": "\"Occasionally\" by 47.96%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "CAT FOOD Types",
            "Top Answer": "\"Complete Dry Food\" by 22.89%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Types Free Range",
            "Top Answer": "\"Occasionally\" by 45.46%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed High Salt/Sodium Content",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 50.2%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FREQUENCY OF EATING AND DRINKING Frequency of Eating and Drinking Cooked Meats (Pre-packed and Unpackaged)",
            "Top Answer": "\"2 or 3 times a WEEK\" by 30.04%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed High Cholesterol Content",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Limit Sometimes\" by 47.61%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Types Vegetarian Ranges",
            "Top Answer": "\"Never\" by 48.72%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "DOG FOOD Brands",
            "Top Answer": "\"Supermarket Own Brand\" by 20.12%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "MEAT ALTERNATIVES (Including TOFU) (Main Shopper) Brands",
            "Top Answer": "\"Quorn\" by 9.03%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FREQUENCY OF EATING AND DRINKING Frequency of Eating and Drinking Vegetarian Products",
            "Top Answer": "\"Never\" by 32.05%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD AND DIET Statements I always make sure I eat the recommended (5 a day) portions of fruit and vegetable every day",
            "Top Answer": "\"Any Agree\" by 40.83%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD AND DIET Statements Tend To Agree",
            "Top Answer": "\"I can't eat as healthily when I am trying to save on food costs\" by 33.64%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "CAT FOOD Brands",
            "Top Answer": "\"Supermarket Own Brand\" by 13.24%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD & DRINK PURCHASING/NUTRITION Consumed Dairy Products",
            "Top Answer": "\"I Take No Notice\" by 49.11%"
        },
        {
            "Question": "FOOD AND DIET Statements Tend To Disagree",
            "Top Answer": "\"I can't eat as healthily when I am trying to save on food costs\" by 29.67%"
        }
    ]
}